>> Kyle Simpson: 那么现在，如果我们以严格方式翻转，您将
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
now if we flip on strict mode, which you
通过将此严格方式片段置于任何作用域的顶部，最好是在
do by putting this strict mode fragment
at the top of any scope, preferably at
程序的顶部，文件顶部或任何功能的顶部。
the top of your program, the top of your
file, or at the top of any function.
如果开启严格方式，那么将发生所有相同的处理。
If you turn on strict mode, all
the same processing is going to happen.
因此，既然我们已经经历过这一点，我们就不必再费力地处理这个问题了。
So since we've run through this, we don't
have to keep belaboring this point.
但当我们到达这条线时我们说
But when we arrive at this line and
we say, hey,
其他类别的范围，我有这个目标的参考，这个题目是听过的。
scope of other class, I have this target
reference for topic ever heard of it.
没有蓝色大理石我们到全球范围说
There's no blue marble,
we go to the global scope and we say,
全球范围都有你听过的话题
global scope have you ever heard of topic,
and
全局作用域类型 : >> 演讲者 1: 否
the global scope kind of respond with
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: No
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 参考错误，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Reference error,
从没听说过
never heard of it.
这是一种不同于类型错误的错误。
That's a different kind of
error than a type error.
当您发现变量及其值时，输入错误。
Type errors are when you found
the variable and the value that it is
目前持有的不合法，不做你想做的事情。
currently holding is not legal to do
whatever you're trying to do with it.
与执行函数一样，访问未定义的 Null 上的属性，
Like execute a function,
access a property on an undefined null,
这种情况是错误的
things like that, that's type error.
参考错误，我找不到那个变量，
A reference error is,
I couldn't find that variable,
我不能给你一个变量好吗
I can't give you a variable to use, okay?
这就是我们希望在所有时间发生的事情。
That's what we would like
to happen all of the time.
现在，由于严格方式的结果而发生引用错误。
It now happens as the result of strict
mode, you get a reference error.
对不起，没有大理石，运气不好。
Sorry, no marble, tough luck.
所以有很多原因有很多理由
So one of the many,
many reasons why it would be good for
你要用严格的方式
you to be using strict mode.
它会避免这样的错误，它几乎肯定是个错误，
It will avoid mistakes like this,
cuz it almost certainly a mistake,
你不应该故意去创造全球的，是吗 ?
it should not be something you
intentionally try to create global, yes?
>> 演讲者 1: 严格方式始终在 ES6 上
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Is strict
mode always pretty on ES6
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 严格方式不是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Strict mode is not
一直都是
always on.
像泡泡之类的工具
It's true that tools like Bubble and
其他的人总是把严格的方式放在那里
other transpilers basically always
put the strict mode in there for you.
所以如果你用的是密码
So if you're using transpired code,
几乎可以确定您的代码在严格的方式下运行。
it was almost a virtual certainty that
your code is running in strict mode.
但是 JavaScript 不是缺省的严格方式，因为这样会破坏一个
But JavaScript is not default the strict
mode because then that would break a bunch
节目的相关信息。
of programs.
那是 20 年前写的
So that were written 20 years ago or
something.
因此，由于向后兼容，您总是必须选择严格的方式。
So because of backwards compatible, you
will always have to opt into strict mode.
在 ES6 内部的某些类型的机制中的另一个小问题
Another little caveat inside of certain
kinds of mechanisms within ES6 and
在前进的过程中，它被认为处于严格模式。
going forward,
it is assumed to be in strict mode.
所以你甚至都没有输入，所以在课里面的时候就可以说，
So you don't even type it, so inside of
a class to talk about later in the course,
或 ES6 模块内部，稍后我们将在此单元中讨论。
or inside of ES6 module,
which we'll talk about later in this unit.
在这两种情况下，假设严格模式，你都不需要
Inside of both of those, strict mode
is assumed, you don't even have to put
严格方式，仅假定代码在严格方式下运行。
the strict mode, is just assume that,
that code is running in strict mode.
但作为一般规则
But as a general rule for
JavaScript 本身不处于严格模式，除非您选择。
JavaScript itself,
it's not in strict mode unless you opt-in.
严格的方式你应该知道的是
What you should know about strict mode is,
它本质上是语言的未来
it's essentially the future
of the language, more and
更多的将类似于类和模块并采用严格方式。
more will be like classes and
modules and assume the strict mode.
所以你最好直接咬那颗子弹
So you might as well just go ahead and
bite that bullet.
大约十年来，它已经存在了将近十年。
It's been around now for
almost a decade basically a decade.
所以如果你不是用严格的方式
So it's definitely time if
you're not using strict mode,
你先把痛和开关给我吧
go ahead and take the pain and
switch, yes?
>> 演讲者 1: 如果您不使用严格的内容，那么有更新的功能将不起作用吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: If you don't use strict
are there newer features that won't work?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 他们有时会谈论或讨论，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: They do
sometimes talk about or discuss,
此功能仅在严格方式或非严格方式下工作。
this feature will only work a certain
way in strict mode or not-strict mode.
因为如果他们添加了一个新功能
Because if they add a new feature,
他们在 20 年前就没有机会破解某人的密码了
they don't have any chances of having
broken somebody's code from 20 years ago.
我不知道有什么特别的例子
I'm not aware of any
specific examples where this
如果您未在严格方式下切换，那么语法不可用。
syntax is not even available,
if you haven't switched on strict mode.
但在这种可能性的范围内，
But it is certainly within the realm of
possibility that things like that may
或者这些行为将不同。
occur, or
that behaviors will be different.
就像我们在这里看到的那样，可以有细微差别的行为。
There can be nuanced different behaviors,
like we're seeing here.
一个可能是允许的，另一个可能不允许。
One might be permissive and
one might be not.
另一个严格方式有区别的示例
Another example of strict
mode having a difference and
它与 ES6 无关
it has nothing to do with ES6.
回到 ES5，当引入严格模式时，
Back in ES5,
when strict mode was introduced,
我们有几种不同的错误如果你不在
we had several different kinds of
errors that if you were not in
严格的方式是错误的，但都是无声的，只是没有发生。
strict mode they were errors, but they
were silent, they just nothing happened.
例如，尝试分配到只读属性，或者
So for example, trying to assign
to a read only property, or
一个只读变量，它只会默默地不做任何事情。
a read only variable,
it just would silently not do anything.
它不会实际执行任务。
It wouldn't actually do the assignment.
一旦开启严格方式，现在就开始为这些错误获取错误。
Once you turn on strict mode,
now you start getting errors for those.
因此，可以观察到的行为有不同的结果，但是
So there are differences in observable
behavior as a result of that, but
我也不会说有太多的特点是你不能
I wouldn't necessarily say that there's a
lot of ostensible features that you can't
在没有它们的情况下使用 >> 演讲者 1: 问题，因此
use without them
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Question, so
这个话题呢，在严格的模式下，总是要定的，对，差不多吗 ?
the topic, in strict mode, they always
have to be defined, right, pretty much?
我的问题是，如果主题在全球范围内，仍然是同一错误，对吗 ?
My question is if topic was in a global
scope, it's still the same error, right?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不知道。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I don't know.
>> 演讲者 1: 如果 - >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果第 7 行
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: If the-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If line 7 was in
全球范围?
the global scope?
>> 扬声器 1: 精确。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，是的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Exactly.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> 扬声器 1: 它还会爆炸吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: It would still blow up?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 它还在爆炸中。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It still blows up.
>> 扬声器 1: 好，全部。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Okay, that's all.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 您不能自动创建变量，必须声明这些变量。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You cannot auto create
variables, you have to declare them.